[{"question": " hey.", "answer": " what&#146;s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " someone on the subway licked my neck! licked my neck!!", "answer": " oh willie&#146;s still alive!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what are you guys doing?", "answer": " oh, my mom called, they&#146;re gonna run our engagement announcement in the local paper, so we&#146;re looking for a good picture of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " oooh, i&#146;m afraid that does not exist.", "answer": " that&#146;s not true, there are great pictures of us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh my god! that&#146;s the creep that you&#146;re with at the statue of liberty.", "answer": " i don&#146;t know what it is, i just can&#146;t take a good picture.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  oh, here&#146;s a great one.", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m not in that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i know, but look at me all tan.", "answer": " hey, why don&#146;t you guys go, get portraits done by a professional photographer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yeah that&#146;s great! next to that, chandler won&#146;t look so stupid.", "answer": " chandler what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  dude, that reverse lay-up! oh&#133;", "answer": " how about those three pointers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " amazing!", "answer": " and those guys were this  close to lettin&#146; us play this time too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey look-look, phoebe&#146;s talking to uh, cute coffeehouse guy.", "answer": " oh, you guys call him cute coffeehouse guy, we call him hums while he pees.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yes, and we call ross lingers in the bathroom.", "answer": "  hey you guys, hums while he pees just asked me out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey, i thought that guy was married.", "answer": " he is! but he&#146;s getting divorced&#151;ross! maybe you know him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " it&#146;s not a club.", "answer": " phoebe, if this guy&#146;s going through a divorce, is it such a good idea to start going out with him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey, divorced men are not bad men!", "answer": " they have that on the napkins at the club.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh, i gotta get back to work.", "answer": " you don&#146;t have to be back for a half-hour!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " yeah but, my assistant tag does sit-ups in the office during lunch. ohh! i could just spread him on a cracker.", "answer": " rach, if you have a crush on this guy, why would you hire him? i mean y&#146;know you can&#146;t date him right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh no, i know that. i know that. although, we made a joke that we spend so much time together he should call me his work wife.", "answer": " soon he&#146;ll be able to call you, that lady he knew who got fired.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i am not gonna get fired, because i&#146;m not gonna act on it.", "answer": " so you wouldn&#146;t mind if he was dating someone else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " why? is he? he is! isn&#146;t he? he&#146;s dating that slut in marketing!", "answer": " maybe i should open a divorced men&#146;s club.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " dude that is so sad.", "answer": " i could put uh-uh a basketball court in the back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, no sit-ups today tag?", "answer": " i just did them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh, well drop and give me ten more!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " uh, i-i had a drink with lunch. did those cost reports come in?", "answer": " yeah, i filled them out last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey rachel!", "answer": "  ahh, hi! hi! melissa, what&#146;s up? i&#146;m just uh, about to umm, go out to the store to get some stuff to put in my backpack. y&#146;know, like dried fruit and granola and stuff. what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " umm, is tag here?", "answer": " no. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh, i was gonna talk to him about doing something tonight.", "answer": " really?! got a little crush on tag there do ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " well, we&#146;ve been flirting back and forth, but i was hoping that tonight it would turn into something a little more than that.", "answer": " okay, whoa-whoa easy there melissa! this ain&#146;t a locker room, okay? but, y&#146;know i remember him saying that-that he had plans tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh no!", "answer": " oh yeah. all right, back to work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hey! isn&#146;t that tag&#146;s backpack.", "answer": " yeah melissa, i don&#146;t want to be known as the uh, office bitch, but i will call your supervisor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  great! that&#146;s great monica! great! now, chandler, you want to give us a smile?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, is the seat uncomfortable?", "answer": " no, i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " chandler, listen to me sweetie, i know you can do this. okay? you have a beautiful smile.", "answer": " i do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah!  all right, maybe you don&#146;t have to smile. let&#146;s try something else. let&#146;s try umm, try looking sexy.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hi joey! what are you doing here?", "answer": " uhh, well i&#146;ve got an audition down the street and i spilled sauce all over the front of my shirt.  you got an extra one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " great.  you got anything that&#146;s not ralph lauren?", "answer": " yeah, i don&#146;t think so joe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " all right, i guess this will be fine.", "answer": " hey, listen umm, what-what are you doing tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " nothing, why?", "answer": " how would you feel about taking out my assistant tag? i&#146;ll pay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " huh, rach i got to say it&#146;s gonna take a lot of money for me to go out on a date with a dude.", "answer": " i&#146;m not asking you to go on a date with him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " really? &#145;cause i could kinda use the money.", "answer": " joey, just-just he-he&#146;s new in town and i know he doesn&#146;t have any guy friends. just take him to like a ball game or something. i&#146;ll really appreciate it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " yeah, okay.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " sure, no problem.  ooh&#151;hey, donuts!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i know. let&#146;s try a look&#133;of far off&#133;wonderment. okay, we&#146;ll-we&#146;ll gaze into our future and we&#146;ll think about our marriage and the days to come.  chandler! what is the matter with your face?! i mean this picture is supposed to say &quot;geller and bing to be married,&quot; not &quot;local woman saves drowning moron!&quot;  hey! don&#146;t laugh at him! he&#146;s my drowning moron!", "answer": " aww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i like this one.  it seems to say, &quot;i love you and that&#146;s why i have to kill you.&quot;", "answer": " they can&#146;t all be bad.  find the one where you make your bedroom eyes. ohh, there it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh my god! those are my bedroom eyes?! why did you ever sleep with me?", "answer": " do you really want to pull at that thread?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i&#146;m having a really good time! hums while he pees: me too! i&#146;m sorry that guy in the subway licked your neck.", "answer": " ohh. no that&#146;s okay, he&#146;s a friend. hums while he pees: hey uh, i don&#146;t mean to be presumptuous but i have these two tickets to the ballroom dancing finals tomorrow night if you want to go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " yeah, i&#133; well y&#146;know i-i mean i missed the-the semi-finals, so i&#146;d just be lost. hums while he pees: i know it&#146;s really lame, but i got these tickets from my boss and&#151;oh no! no! no! my god!", "answer": " okay, don&#146;t freak out. i&#146;ll go. hums while he pees: no it&#146;s&#133; uh, my ex-wife whitney is out there. i cannot deal with her right now. that woman is crazy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay, i know. hold on.  hey ross?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " yeah, umm that&#146;s whitney , kyle&#146;s ex-wife out there, now do you think that you can y&#146;know divert her so that we can slip out?", "answer": " what?! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " hi ginger.", "answer": " all right! i want my key back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " i don&#146;t have it!", "answer": " it&#146;s right there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " look, i&#146;m sorry but you-you-you better go pheebs.", "answer": " all right, well i just wanted to say thank you though for diverting kyle&#146;s ex.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh yeah&#151;no&#151;you&#146;re welcome. we&#146;ll talk about it later.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hi whitney.", "answer": " hi ross! you ready for breakfast?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yep.  okay.", "answer": "  kyle&#146;s ex-wife? you were supposed to divert her not date her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  hi! i&#146;m sorry, but can you give me a second while i talk to this woman, who by the way did not spend the night.", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " okay.   i did divert her and we ended up having a great time! okay?", "answer": " watching ballroom dancing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yes! that&#146;s where we realized we were both super cool people!", "answer": " well look-look, okay ross, kyle just told me some really bad stuff about her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " like what?", "answer": " like she&#146;s really mean, and she&#146;s over critical, and-and&#151;no! she will paint a room a really bright color without even checking with you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " and! she uses sex as a weapon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " fine! thank you for warning me. at breakfast i&#146;ll be on full alert for room painting and sex weapons.", "answer": " you&#146;re still gonna go out with her?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " well, didn&#146;t you just hear what i said?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " pheebs come on! i mean, consider the source! of course her ex-husband&#146;s gonna say that stuff. now, if you&#146;ll excuse me&#133;", "answer": "  no listen to me! she is crazy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  uh, your door isn&#146;t sound proof.", "answer": " you see? nothing is good enough for her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " good morning.", "answer": " hi tag! hey, so did you have fun with uh, with joey last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh yeah! we went to the knicks game.", "answer": " ohh that&#146;s nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " then we went to this bar and he hooked us up with all these women!", "answer": " wo-women? you mean like old women?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well kinda old, like 30.", "answer": "  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " and i never used to be able to just talk to girls in bars, but i got like 20 phone numbers last night.", "answer": " that&#146;s great! wow man, so joey must&#146;ve really taught you some stuff huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " a little.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " see? that&#146;s a great smile! easy. natural. now, pretend i have a camera.  you&#146;re changing it!", "answer": " i can&#146;t help it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " all right, all right, all right, all right, you wanna know what i do when i take resume shots?", "answer": " borrow money from me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay, first&#151;first of all, you want to make it look spontaneous. i look down , look down, keep looking down; then i look up.  see? all right, now you try. look down , you&#146;re looking down, keep looking down&#133;", "answer": " why is there jelly on your shoe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so uh, heard you had some fun with tag last night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yeah! that guy&#146;s all right!", "answer": " yeah and you had fun teaching him how to be all joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " y&#146;know, all the women.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " hey well, you can&#146;t teach someone to be good with women. y&#146;know, that&#146;s why i never had any luck with chandler.", "answer": "  i&#146;m right here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " all right, would-would you mind just not going out with him again? okay, just the idea of you and he and all these women, it&#146;s just&#151;and i know he&#146;s my assistant and i can&#146;t date him&#151;but it just bothers me, all right?!", "answer": " hey! no-no-no-no, you can&#146;t take him away from me! i got a great partner to pick up girls with! finally!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i&#146;m still right here!", "answer": " all right, will you, will you at least tell him how hollow and unsatisfying this, dating tons of women thing is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  what?!", "answer": " i just don&#146;t want him to meet anybody until i am over my crush&#151;and i will get over it. it&#146;s-it&#146;s not like i love him, it&#146;s just physical! but&#151;i mean i get crushes like this all the time! i mean hell, i had a crush on you when i first met ya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i know, monica told me.", "answer": " did you have a crush on me, when you first met me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": "  so, will you talk to him?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know rach.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh, come on! i&#146;ll give you ten free ralph lauren shirts.", "answer": " one!  no ten! you said ten! you can&#146;t take that back!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " hey joey, you wanted to talk to me?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know. you uh, you got something for me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " ten. okay. now tag there&#146;s such a thing as to many women.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  hey! there you are!", "answer": " there i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " are you okay?", "answer": " yeah, joey said i uh, i needed to relax so he gave me an antihistamine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah, and then i fell asleep on the subway and went all the way to brooklyn. brooklyn is f-far!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " chandler, what were you thinking?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, but don&#146;t worry, don&#146;t worry, because i know how to take a picture now.  okay, see? look down , look down, look down&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": "  yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " so, how are things going with crazy? has she cooked your rabbit yet?", "answer": " listen, you are hearing one side of the story, okay&#151;and f.y.i she must&#146;ve shown kyle over 30 paint samples before she painted that room! and his response to each one was, &quot;i don&#146;t give a tiny rat&#146;s ass.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yeah well, maybe she should&#146;ve spent a little less time decorating and a little more time in the bedroom.", "answer": " well, i don&#146;t think we are gonna have that problem, but maybe that&#146;s just because i am not emotionally unavailable!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you think he&#146;s emotionally unavailable?", "answer": " i think he can be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " well, maybe he wouldn&#146;t be she didn&#146;t bring the office home every night!", "answer": " well, excuse her for knowing what she wants to do with her life!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " yeah well, she certainly knew what she was doing new year&#146;s eve 1997.", "answer": "  i knew you were gonna throw that in my face!! that was three years ago! she apologized and she apologized! what more do you want?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": "  we want the last six years back!!", "answer": " so do we!! so do we!!  i&#146;m sorry you had to see that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " good morning rachel.", "answer": " hi!  thanks, hey so uh what&#146;d you do last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " went out with joey.", "answer": " oh yeah? another night of birdogging the chickas?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " no. we had a really good talk. i don&#146;t think i&#146;m gonna do that bar scene anymore.", "answer": " wow! i did not see that coming.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " it&#146;s just not really who i am. y'know, i&#146;ve always been happier when&#133;why am i telling you this? you don&#146;t care about this stuff.", "answer": " oh no, yes i do! i do! i mean, come on go on, you were, you were saying i am happier when uh, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " when i&#146;m in a relationship, i love having a girlfriend.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " someone i can spoil, y&#146;know?", "answer": " sp-spoil?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " uh-huh! let me ask you something?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " do you believe that there is one perfect person for everyone?", "answer": " well, i-i&#146;m startin&#146; too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " and if that person is already in your life, you should do something about it right?", "answer": " yes! hell yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " all right then, it&#146;s settled.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " i&#146;m gettin&#146; back together with my ex-girlfriend.", "answer": " i&#146;d love to!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " what?", "answer": "  hello?!  oh, yeah!  this is gonna be a while. excuse me.  yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " my god!", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry. is that annoying? and speaking about being selfish in bed, how&#146;s whitney?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " well maybe she wouldn&#146;t have to be selfish in bed if someone else knew where everything was!", "answer": " oh he knows!  for the most part.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " oh hey! good, you&#146;re both here.", "answer": " we kinda need to talk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " both of you together?", "answer": " wh-what&#146;s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " well, i went over to kyle&#146;s last night to pick up a few things and we got to reminiscing&#133;", "answer": " &#133;we talked through most of the night and we realized that the reason we were so angry at each other was because there are still feelings there. so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oh just say it kyle!", "answer": " we&#146;re gonna give it another try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " what about her whining and her constant need for attention?!", "answer": " i&#146;m gonna work on that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh right, because you&#146;re so capable of change.", "answer": "  y&#146;know, he hums when he pees!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i do know.", "answer": " it makes him miss the bowl, but whatever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " that&#146;s all right, we-we don&#146;t need you. in fact, hey i&#146;m over it already.", "answer": " yeah, and y&#146;know what? i don&#146;t give a tiny rat&#146;s ass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  i&#146;m sorry. ugh, pheebs, you were, you were right about her. y&#146;know, she did try to use sex as a weapon! yeah, i hurt my back a little.", "answer": " oh. y&#146;know, he hums while he does other stuff to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " yeah, were better off without them.", "answer": " and y&#146;know, even if they break up again, you&#146;d better not let him in your sad men&#146;s club!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " divorced men&#146;s club.", "answer": " potato, potaato.  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " hey guys check it out! my mom sent me the paper!", "answer": " ooh, let&#146;s see it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " ahhh.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh yeah, that looks good.", "answer": " you guys make a very attractive couple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " yeah, we look great together.", "answer": " yeah, we really do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " wow! imagine what our kids would look like!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " y&#146;know, we don&#146;t have to imagine.", "answer": " i&#146;m marrying her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep5.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}]